Caribbean people, I really need us to get it together.
I've got a bunch of Jamaicans under a previous post saying that Jamaica is not owned by the UK.
Jamaica and several other Caribbean islands are still a part of the Commonwealth, including Grenada.
Similar to Africa, which is why I call the Caribbean the Africa of the Western Hemisphere,
independence has been by and large a performance.
It has been a guise because our nations are still ruled by banks and loans and trade that we do not get to control.
Our resources, our economies, our labor, our mind by outside sources who tell us what the price is going to be.
Yes, we may have prime ministers.
Yes, we may have MPs.
Yes, we may look like we're making the decisions.
And you all say things like, yeah, but King Charles, you know, he is just a figurehead.
Is that what you think?
You think they sit up in that big old place and all they are are just fodder for tabloids?
Is that what y'all really, really think?
Or is that simply what you tell yourself?
Because your ego refuses to acknowledge the fact that we're still not free.
Because until we acknowledge that, we are still continuing the cycle and the consistency of colonialism.
No Jamaica, no Grenada, no Trinidad, no Barbados, no St. Kitts and Nevis, no St. Vincent, no St. Croix, no Anguilla.
No, I can go on and on and on.
We're not free.
The colonizers, whether they are the British or the Dutch or the United States, et cetera, are still doing the work of colonization.
We're not free until we can be food sovereign, until we are able to have our own deals for oil based on our own money, and until our school curriculums on these islands and in these nations reflect that.
They only just don't stop wearing the white wig and the damn cortos.
Please.
We're all slaves, and you love it.